day2dayprinting.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Day2Day Printing

  * ####  Protecting your privacy is paramount for the success of our business

We have adapted technologies and operating procedures that support the privacy of our clients. We use encryption for sensitive information such as Credit Card data. To further ensure that your privacy is completely protected, we have adapted security clearance levels and personal background check for employees in processing and accounting department of day2dayprinting.com.

  * ####  Registration

Day2dayprinting.com provides products and services to the public & businesses. Creating a username and password will allow you to use day2dayprinting.com most securely and place an order.. Creating an account also allows you to review all of your orders, review your proofs, receive our free giveaway promotional offers, re-order with ease, and keep track of your designs and shipping options.

  * ####  Use of information policy

Day2dayprinting.com is the sole owner and user of the information you provide. We use your provided information to send you updates regarding shipping and tracking information of your order, order process updates, file approval. Unless instructed otherwise, we may also use your information to send you news regarding free product offering, promotions, discounts, special offers, and change of policies. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited.

We do NOT share, rent, lease or sell any of your information to any other company or vendors that we may use to produce products.

  * ####  Security policy

Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is theindustry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. Itencrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannotbe read over the internet.

  * ####  Cancellation and Refund

For order cancellations, please notify us immediately at (877) 436-6177. Cancellations must be made before you have approved your PDF proof to avoid any processing charges. If production has already begun, our customer service representatives will inform you of any cancellation charges. No refund will be issued for services such as PDF proofs, hard copy proofs, design services, marketing information, and business consulting. We do not issue refunds once an order has been sent to pre-press. Day2Day Printing reserves the right to charge the client for any services performed on the job up to the point of cancellation.

Since all products are custom made and have no resale value, we cannot issue refunds for already processed orders. However, we will gladly reprint your order and ship it to you at no cost, given at least one of the following apply:

    * Your product has production related defects
    * Your product is damaged in transit due to inappropriate packaging by the Day2Day Printing facility

Please contact us within three business days after receiving your order for a reprint request. If you didn't receive your order due to shipping issues, please notify our customer service representatives at (877) 436-6177. We may ask that you return your damaged order for further analysis. Day2Day Printing will pay for all return shipping costs of damaged orders.

Reprints are done with the same order specifications and originally submitted file. Reprint orders are processed as next day orders and shipped with originally agreed shipping terms.

  * ####  Legal disclaimer

Although we strive to protect your private information from any other third party, we may share necessary information with third party vendors such as UPS, FedEx, USPS and DHL, and other freight companies.

  * ####  Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of electronic data that are stored in user's computer. They are only placed on user's computer if the browser setting allows cookies from secure sites. Day2Day Printing used cookies to collect and analyze visit statistics and we use those statistics to improve our website in order to provide you with higher quality of personalized user experience. We use cookies to track visitor's interaction with our website as well as using third party cookies to serve ads to a particular interest groups. You can opt out of interest-based advertising by visiting Network Advertising Initiative and selecting the platforms you would want to opt out of.

  * ####  Communication

We will communicate with you in regards to your orders or our services only. Our Client Service Personnel will use your phone number, email address, cell phone number, and addresses to contact you via phone calls, emails, text messages to communicate issues or updates regarding your orders.

  * ####  Links

Day2dayprinting.com may contain links to other websites. We do not in anyway sponsor or verify the content of other websites that are linked to day2dayprinting.com or vendors you may visit through day2dayprinting.com. Please read the privacy statements of other sites you visit. All of the privacy statements and policies appearing on day2dayprinting.com apply only to the day2dayprinting.com website.

  * ####  Change in policies

Day2dayprinting.com has discretion to change or update this privacy policy at any time. However, we will notify our clients via email in regards to any changes we have made to our policies. We suggest you check our policies on a regular basis to stay informed of any updates that may have implemented. Continued use of our service indicates your agreement to our terms and conditions and policies.

  * ####  Contact information
